Guide to the Sports Information Office Records, 1932-ongoing UA.13.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- UA2013-0034, 1927-2015
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Wake Forest, 2012-02-28 (Box UA2013-0034.193)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. North Carolina, 2012-03-02 (Box UA2013-0034.193)
  - Men's Basketball: ACC Tournament: Duke vs. Virginia Tech, 2012-03-09 (Box UA2013-0034.193)
  - Men's Basketball: ACC Tournament: Duke vs. Florida State, 2012-03-10 (Box UA2013-0034.193)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament: Duke vs Lehigh, 2012-03-16 (Box UA2013-0034.193)
  - Men's Basketball: China and Dubai, circa 2019-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.193)
  - Men's Basketball: Countdown to Craziness, 2011-10-15 (Box UA2013-0034.193)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Bellarmine, 2011-10-29 (Box UA2013-0034.193)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Shaw, 2011-11-02 (Box UA2013-0034.193)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Belmont, 2011-11-11 (Box UA2013-0034.193)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Presbyterian, 2011-11-12 (Box UA2013-0034.193)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Michigan State, 2011-11-15 (Box UA2013-0034.193)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Davidson, 2011-11-18 (Box UA2013-0034.193)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Tennessee, 2011-11-21 (Box UA2013-0034.193)
  - Men's Basketball: EA Sports Maui Invitational Semifinals, 2011-11-22 (Box UA2013-0034.193)
  - Men's Basketball: EA Sports Maui Invitational Championship, 2011-11-23 (Box UA2013-0034.193)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Ohio State, 2011-11-29 (Box UA2013-0034.193)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Colorado State, 2011-12-07 (Box UA2013-0034.193)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Washington, 2011-12-10 (Box UA2013-0034.194)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. UNC Greensboro, 2011-12-19 (Box UA2013-0034.194)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Western Michigan, 2011-12-30 (Box UA2013-0034.194)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Pennsylvania, 2012-01-01 (Box UA2013-0034.194)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Temple, 2012-01-04 (Box UA2013-0034.194)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Georgia Tech, 2012-01-07 (Box UA2013-0034.194)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia, 2012-01-12 (Box UA2013-0034.194)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Clemson, 2012-01-15 (Box UA2013-0034.194)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Radford, 2009-11-21 (Box UA2013-0034.194)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Arizona State, 2009-11-25 (Box UA2013-0034.194)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Connecticut, 2009-11-27 (Box UA2013-0034.194)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Wisconsin, 2009-12-02 (Box UA2013-0034.194)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. St. John's, 2009-12-05 (Box UA2013-0034.194)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Gardner-Webb, 2009-12-15 (Box UA2013-0034.194)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Gonzaga, 2009-12-19 (Box UA2013-0034.194)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Long Beach State, 2009-12-29 (Box UA2013-0034.194)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Pennsylvania, 2009-12-31 (Box UA2013-0034.194)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Clemson, 2010-01-03 (Box UA2013-0034.195)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Iowa State, 2010-01-06 (Box UA2013-0034.195)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Georgia Tech, 2010-01-09 (Box UA2013-0034.195)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Boston College, 2010-01-13 (Box UA2013-0034.195)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Wake Forest, 2010-01-17 (Box UA2013-0034.195)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. NC State, 2010-01-20 (Box UA2013-0034.195)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Clemson, 2010-01-23 (Box UA2013-0034.195)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Florida State, 2010-01-27 (Box UA2013-0034.195)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Georgetown, 2010-01-30 (Box UA2013-0034.195)
  - Men's Basketball: ACC Tournament, 2006-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.195)
  - Men's Basketball: ACC Tournament Media Guides, 2006-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.195)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament 1st Round, 2006-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.195)
  - Men's Basketball, 2007-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.196)
  - Men's Basketball, 2007-02-01 (Box UA2013-0034.196)
  - Men's Basketball, 2007-01-01 (Box UA2013-0034.196)
  - Men's Basketball, 2006-10-01 (Box UA2013-0034.196)
  - Men's Basketball, 2006-11-01 (Box UA2013-0034.196)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2006-12-01 (Box UA2013-0034.196)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament 1st Round, 2006-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.196)
  - Men's Basketball: Preseason, 2006-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.196)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Charlotte, 2009-11-17 (Box UA2013-0034.197)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Coastal Carolina, 2009-11-16 (Box UA2013-0034.197)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. UNC-Greensboro, 2009-11-13 (Box UA2013-0034.197)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Findlay, 2009-11-03 (Box UA2013-0034.197)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Pfeiffer, 2009-10-24 (Box UA2013-0034.197)
  - Men's Basketball: Countdown to Craziness, 2009-10-16 (Box UA2013-0034.197)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, January to May 2009 (Box UA2013-0034.197)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2009-06-01 (Box UA2013-0034.197)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2009-07-01 (Box UA2013-0034.197)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, August 2009; September 2009 (Box UA2013-0034.197)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2009-10-01 (Box UA2013-0034.197)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2009-11-01 (Box UA2013-0034.197)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2009-12-01 (Box UA2013-0034.197)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2010-01-01 (Box UA2013-0034.197)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2010-02-01 (Box UA2013-0034.198)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2010-03-01 (Box UA2013-0034.198)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2010-04-01 (Box UA2013-0034.198)
  - Men's Basketball: Recruits, 2009-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.198)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Florida State; Duke vs. UNC, March 3, 2009; March 8, 2009 (Box UA2013-0034.198)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Boston College; Duke vs. University of Maryland, March 13, 2009; March 14, 2009 (Box UA2013-0034.198)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Florida State; Duke vs. Binghamton, March 15, 2009; March 19, 2009 (Box UA2013-0034.198)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Texas; Duke vs. Villanova, March 21, 2009; March 26, 2009 (Box UA2013-0034.198)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament History, 2008-2009 (Box UA2013-0034.198)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box UA2013-0034.198)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2008-2009 (Box UA2013-0034.199)
  - Men's Basketball: Game Stats, 2008-2009 (Box UA2013-0034.199)
  - Men's Basketball: Recruiting, 2008-2009 (Box UA2013-0034.199)
  - Men's Basketball: Sports Illustrated, 2005-11-21; 3 Volumes (Box UA2013-0034.199)
  - Men's Basketball: Blue vs. White, 2005-10-22 (Box UA2013-0034.199)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Concordia; Duke vs. NC Central, November 3, 2005; November 10; 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.199)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Boston University; Duke vs. Seton Hall, November 14, 2005; November 16, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.199)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Davidson, 2005-11-19 (Box UA2013-0034.199)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Drexel; Duke vs. Memphis, November 23, 2005; November 25, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.199)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Indiana; Duke vs. Virginia Tech, November 30, 2005; December 4, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.199)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Pennsylvania; Duke vs. Texas, December 7, 2005; December 10, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.199)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Valparaiso; Duke vs. St. John's, December 18, 2005; December 21, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.200)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. UNC-Greensboro; Duke vs. Bucknell, December 31, 2005; January 2, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.200)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Wake Forest; Duke vs. Maryland, January 8, 2006; January 11, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.200)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Clemson; Duke vs. NC State, January 14, 2006; January 18, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.200)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Georgetown; Duke vs. Virginia Tech, January 21, 2006; January 26, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.200)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia; Duke vs. Boston College, January 28, 2006; February 1, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.200)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Florida State; Duke vs. North Carolina, February 4, 2006; February 7, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.200)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland; Duke vs. Wake Forest, February 11, 2006; February 14, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.200)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Miami; Duke vs. Georgia Tech, February 19, 2006; February 22, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.201)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Temple; Duke vs. Florida State, February 25, 2006; March 1, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.201)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. North Carolina, 2006-03-04 (Box UA2013-0034.201)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos and Yearbooks, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.201)
  - Men's Basketball: ACC Men's Tournament, March 9-12, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.201)
  - Men's Basketball: ACC Tournament Guides, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.201)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Rounds 1 & 2, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.201)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Rounds 1 & 2 Media Guides, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.202)
  - Men's Basketball: Preseason, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.202)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, November-December 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.202)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2006-01-01 (Box UA2013-0034.202)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2006-02-01 (Box UA2013-0034.202)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2006-03-01 (Box UA2013-0034.202)
  - Men's Basketball: Postseason, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.203)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, April-May 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.203)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 2002-2003 (Box UA2013-0034.203)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Rounds 1 and 2, 2002-2003 (Box UA2013-0034.203)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Rounds 1 and 2 Media Guides, 2002-2003 (Box UA2013-0034.203)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament (Sweet Sixteen), 2002-2003 (Box UA2013-0034.203)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament (Sweet Sixteen) Media Guides, 2002-2003 (Box UA2013-0034.203)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. St. John's, 2008-2009 (Box UA2013-0034.203)
  - Men's Basketball, 1995-1996 (Box UA2013-0034.203)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 2001-2002; 2 folders (Box UA2013-0034.204)
    Includes photographic prints and contact sheets.
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 2000-2001 (Box UA2013-0034.204)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos and Media Guide, 1998-1999 (Box UA2013-0034.204)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1999-2000 (Box UA2013-0034.204)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 2000-2001 (Box UA2013-0034.204)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos and Media Guide, 1990-1991 (Box UA2013-0034.204)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos and Media Guide, 1991-1992 (Box UA2013-0034.204)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1993-1994 (Box UA2013-0034.204)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1994-1995 (Box UA2013-0034.204)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1995-1996 (Box UA2013-0034.204)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1996-1997 (Box UA2013-0034.204)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1997-1998 (Box UA2013-0034.204)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1988-1989 (Box UA2013-0034.204)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos and Media Guide, 1989-1990 (Box UA2013-0034.204)
  - Men's Basketball: Pictures, 1986-1987 (Box UA2013-0034.204)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1987-1988 (Box UA2013-0034.204)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1982-1983 (Box UA2013-0034.204)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1986 (Box UA2013-0034.204)
  - Men's Basketball: Pictures, 1983-1984 (Box UA2013-0034.204)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1980-1982 (Box UA2013-0034.204)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2003-2004 (Box UA2013-0034.205)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1983-1984 (Box UA2013-0034.205)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 1984-1986 (Box UA2013-0034.205)
    includes photographic slides.
  - Men's Basketball: Preseason, 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.205)
  - Men's Basketball: Blue vs. White; Duke vs. EA Sports; Duke vs. Nike Elite, October 25, 2003; November 5, 2003: November 12, 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.205)
  - Men's Basketball: Box Scores, 2003-2004 (Box UA2013-0034.205)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Detroit, 2003-11-22 (Box UA2013-0034.205)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Pacific; Duke vs. Liberty; Duke vs. Purdue, November 27-29, 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.205)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Michigan State; Duke vs. St. John's, December 3, 2003; December 6, 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.205)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Portland; Duke vs. Princeton, December 14, 2003; December 27, 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.205)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Texas; Duke vs. Davidson, December 20, 2003; December 29, 2003 (Box UA2013-0034.205)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia; Duke vs. NC State, January 11, 2004; January 15, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.206)
    Includes digital disks and contact sheets.
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Clemson; Duke vs. Fairfield, January 3, 2004; January 6, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.206)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs Wake Forest; Duke vs. Maryland, January 17, 2004: January 21, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.206)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament, March 26, 2004; March 28, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.206)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Media Guides, 2003-2004 (Box UA2013-0034.206)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Final Four, 2004-04-03 (Box UA2013-0034.206)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Final Four Media Guides, 2003-2004 (Box UA2013-0034.207)
  - Men's Basketball: Blue vs. White; Duke vs. Shaw; Duke vs. Barton College, October 27, 2007; November 1, 2007; November 3, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.207)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. NC Central; Duke vs. New Mexico State; Duke vs. Princeton, November 9, 2007; November 12; 2007; November 19, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.207)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Illinois; Duke vs. Marquette; Duke vs. Eastern Kentucky, November 20, 2007; November 21, 2007; November 25, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.207)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Wisconsin; Duke vs. Davidson; Duke vs. Michigan, November 27, 2007; December 1, 2007; December 8, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.207)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Albany; Duke vs. Pittsburgh; Duke vs. Cornell, December 17, 2007; December 20, 2007; January 6, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.207)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Temple; Duke vs. Virginia; Duke vs. Florida State, January 9, 2008; January 13, 2008; January 16, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.208)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Clemson; Duke vs. Virginia Tech; Duke vs. Maryland, January 19, 2008; January 24, 2008; January 27, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.208)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. NC State; Duke vs. Miami; Duke vs. North Carolina, January 31, 2008; February 2, 2008; February 6, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.208)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Boston College; Duke vs. Maryland; Duke vs. Wake Forest, February 9, 2008; February 13, 2008; February 17, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.208)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Miami; Duke vs. St. John's; Duke vs. Georgia Tech, February 20, 2008; February 23, 2008; February 27, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.209)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. NC State; Duke vs. Virginia; Duke vs. North Carolina, March 1, 2008; March 5, 2008; March 8, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.209)
  - Men's Basketball: ACC Tournament, March 14-15, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.209)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Round 1, 2008-03-20 (Box UA2013-0034.209)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Round 2, 2008-03-22 (Box UA2013-0034.209)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Media Guides, 2007-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.209)
  - Men's Basketball: Banquet Books, circa 2007-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.210)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2007-2008; 2 folders (Box UA2013-0034.210)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, November 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.210)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, December 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.210)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, January 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.210)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, February 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.210)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, March 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.210)
  - Men's Basketball: Recruits, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.210)
  - Men's Basketball: Blue-White Scrimmage; Duke vs. Shaw; Duke vs. NC Central, October 28, 2006; November 2, 2006; November 4, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.210)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Rhode Island; Duke vs. Southern Illinois, November 16, 2008; November 20, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.210)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Michigan; Duke vs. Montana, November 21, 2008; November 23, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.210)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Duquesne; Duke vs. Purdue, November 28, 2008: September 2, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.211)
  - Men's Basketball: Blue-White Scrimmage; Duke vs. Virginia Union; Duke vs. Lenoir-Rhyne, October 18, 2008; October 25, 2008; November 5, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.211)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. University of Maryland; Duke vs. Virginia Tech, February 25, 2009; February 28, 2009 (Box UA2013-0034.211)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. St. John's; Duke vs. Wake Forest, February 19, 2009; February 22, 2009 (Box UA2013-0034.211)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. North Carolina; Duke vs. Boston College, February 11, 2009; February 15, 2009 (Box UA2013-0034.211)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Clemson; Duke vs. Miami, February 4, 2009; February 7, 2009 (Box UA2013-0034.211)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland, 2009-01-24 (Box UA2013-0034.211)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Wake Forest; Duke vs. Virginia, January 28, 2009; February 1, 2009 (Box UA2013-0034.211)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Georgia Tech, 2009-01-14 (Box UA2013-0034.212)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Georgetown, 2009-01-17 (Box UA2013-0034.212)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. NC State, 2009-01-20 (Box UA2013-0034.212)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Davidson, 2009-01-07 (Box UA2013-0034.212)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Florida State, 2009-01-10 (Box UA2013-0034.212)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Xavier, 2008-12-20 (Box UA2013-0034.212)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Loyola (MD), 2008-12-31 (Box UA2013-0034.212)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia Tech, 2009-01-04 (Box UA2013-0034.212)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke Blue-White Scrimmage; Duke vs. St. Francis/Xavier; Duke vs. NC Central, October 23, 2004; November 5, 2004; November 11, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.212)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. UNC Greensboro; Duke vs. Michigan State, November 27, 2004; November 30, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.212)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Valparaiso; Duke vs. Toledo, December 4, 2004; December 12, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.212)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Illinois-Chicago; Duke vs. Oklahoma, December 14, 2004; December 18, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.213)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Clemson; Duke vs. Princeton, January 2, 2005; January 5, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.213)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Temple; Duke vs. NC State, January 8, 2005; January 13, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.213)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia; Duke vs. Miami, January 16, 2005; January 19, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.213)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Florida State; Duke vs. Maryland, January 22, 2005; January 26, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.213)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Virginia Tech; Duke vs. Wake Forest, January 30, 2005; February 2, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.213)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Georgia Tech; Duke vs. North Carolina, February 5, 2005; February 9, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.213)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Maryland; Duke vs. Virginia Tech, February 12, 2005; February 17, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.213)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Wake Forest; Duke vs. Georgia Tech, February 20, 2005; February 23, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.214)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. St. John's; Duke vs. Miami, February 26, 2005; March 3, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.214)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. North Carolina, 2005-03-06 (Box UA2013-0034.214)
  - Men's Basketball: ACC Tournament, March 10-13, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.214)
  - Men's Basketball: ACC Tournament Guides, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.214)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Round 1, 2005-03-17 (Box UA2013-0034.214)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Round 2, 2005-03-20 (Box UA2013-0034.214)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Rounds 1 and 2 Media Guides, 2004-2005; 2 folders (Box UA2013-0034.215)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, October-November 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.215)
  - Men's Basketball: Preseason, 2004-2005 (Box UA2013-0034.215)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2004-11-01 (Box UA2013-0034.215)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Tennessee-Martin; Duke vs. Davidson, November 20, 2004; November 22, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.215)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2004-12-01 (Box UA2013-0034.215)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2005-01-01 (Box UA2013-0034.215)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2005-02-01 (Box UA2013-0034.215)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2005-03-01 (Box UA2013-0034.215)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2005-04-01 (Box UA2013-0034.215)
  - Men's Basketball: Photos, 2004-2005 (Box UA2013-0034.215)
    Includes photographic prints and digital disks.
  - Men's Basketball: Basketball Banquet, 2005-04-21 (Box UA2013-0034.215)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Final Four Media Guides, 2004-2005 (Box UA2013-0034.215)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Georgia Southern, 2008-11-11 (Box UA2013-0034.216)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Michigan, 2008-12-06 (Box UA2013-0034.216)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. UNC-Asheville, 2008-12-17 (Box UA2013-0034.216)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs. Houston, Presbyterian; Duke vs. Georgia Southern, 2008-11-11 (Box UA2013-0034.216)
  - Men's Basketball: Georgia Southern vs. Houston; Duke vs. Presbyterian, 2008-11-10 (Box UA2013-0034.216)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2004-03-01 (Box UA2013-0034.216)
  - Men's Basketball: Clippings, 2004-04-01 (Box UA2013-0034.216)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Round 1 and 2, March 18, 2004; March 20, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.216)
  - Devilirum, 1978-1985; 3 folders (Box UA2013-0034.217)
  - Rowing: Clippings, circa 1978-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.217)
  - Fencing, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.217)
  - Men's Fencing: Clippings, 2009-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.217)
  - Men's Fencing: Clippings, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.217)
  - Men's Fencing: Player Files, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.217)
  - Men's Fencing: Media Guides, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.217)
  - Men's Fencing: Clippings, 2010-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.217)
  - Men's Fencing: Clippings, 2011-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.217)
  - Men's Basketball: Composites Sheet 1, 1992-1993 (Box UA2013-0034.217)
  - Men's Track and Cross Country: Morgan Pearson, circa 1992-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.217)
  - Men's Tennis: Clippings, 2012-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.217)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs Clemson; Duke vs. Virginia, February 8 2004; February 11, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.218)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs Georgia Tech; Duke vs North Carolina, January 31, 2004; February 5, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.218)
  - Men's Basketball: NCAA Tournament Rounds 1 & 2, 2003-2004 (Box UA2013-0034.218)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs Maryland; Duke vs. Valparaiso, February 22, 2004; February 26; 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.218)
  - Men's Lacrosse, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.218)
  - Men's Soccer, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.218)
  - Women's Swimming and Diving; Women's Tennis; Volleyball, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.218)
  - Assorted Team Photos, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.218)
  - Wrestling: Michael Mitchell, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.218)
  - Matt Mapes, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.218)
  - Football: Eckerman, Matt, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.218)
  - Wrestling: Eckerman, Matt, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.218)
  - McElhany, Harold (Hal), circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.218)
  - Falcone, Carmen, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.218)
  - Wrestling: Luke Sharpe, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.218)
  - LeBar, John, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.218)
  - Newman, Ed, circa 1999-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.218)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs NC State; Duke vs Wake Forest, February 15, 2004; February 18, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.219)
  - Men's Basketball: Postseason, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.219)
  - Men's Basketball: ACC Basketball Tournament, March 11-14, 2004; 2 folders (Box UA2013-0034.219)
  - Men's Basketball: Duke vs Florida State; Duke vs Georgia Tech, February 29, 2004; March 3, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.219)